here's what's coming up in the category
hic est, quod suus 'venient in genus
five TV newsroom the Department of
quinque ad Department of TV NEWSROOM
National Defense is joining the fight
Defensionis est pugna National joining
against 5g citing risks to GPS and
5g est contra consuetudinem GPS et metus
military operations Google is serious
armisque gravis Google
about ensuring the pixel line of Android
de stirpe MASCULINUS tuto pixel
phones is secure they've announced that
nuntiatum est quod theyve 'phones secure
they'll pay security researchers up to
quod inquisitores ad securitatem millia talentorum appendam arcariis
1.5 million dollars to find hacks and
1.5 million pupa hacks et inveniam
exploits the official site for the
ipsae enim locum officialis
Monaro digital coin was hacked to
Digital Monaro numerata pecunia est caederetur ruebat
deliver currency stealing malware to
monetæ eripere furtum est malware
users who were downloading wallet
users qui loculus download
software and wouldn't it be nice if
et non sit delicatus si software
there is a Facebook rival well there is
nihil est enim tam Facebook sit aemulus
and it's founded by the guy who built
et aedificavit eam ab homunculo
Wikipedia stick around the full details
Id inhaero circum singula plenum
are coming up later in the show this is
ecce venient usque ad spectaculum post haec
the category five dot TV newsroom
Genus quinque dat TV newsroom
covering the week stop texting with a
obtegere stop texting et sabbatorum
slight Linux bias I'm Sacha Rickman
Linux leve pondus sum Sacha Rickman
joined this week by Jeff Westen here's
per Jeff copulavit hoc septimana scriptor hic Westen
some quick honorable mentions this week
De hoc aliqua honesta velox hebdomadam
Tesla CEO Elon Musk's suggested late
CEO: Elon MOSCHUS Tesla suus 'sero suggesserant
Tuesday that his company had now
Martis erat autem turba quae suum
received 250,000 pre-orders for the
acceperat enim 250,000 precommandes
cyber truck its Blade Runner inspired
Laminas CURSOR cyber salsissimus vir vivens et inspiravit
electric pickup Tesla's unveil event for
RAPINA s ultrices tortor eventus Tesla
its first pickup truck was marred by the
RAPINA salsissimus vir vivens ad primam sollicitae
vehicles window breaking when an
muro fenestram cum vehiculis
executive threw a meatball at them in an
misit eos in efficientia meatball
effort to demo the wall meatball Ron
Vivamus murus meatball labore demo
Burgundy alright well anyways so ladies
Burgundiam petere licet sic bene anyways dominarum
and gentlemen there was a parently a
erat autem et iudices parently
meatball that went through the window
perambulabat autem meatball fenestram
you know just keep going after the
ut cognoscatis, sicut post exitum
meatball Jeff it turns out the same test
Idem evenit meatball Jeff amet
was performed before that went perfectly
et factum est in conspectu perfectly
the car's trapezoid shape was also
etiam trapezium figura cars '
mocked in various memes even at the
usque ad memes variis illudit
official social media pages for Lego
Paginae publica socialis instrumentis Lego
had their go at the cyber truck but
erant autem in ire ad cyber salsissimus vir vivens
included innovative modular roof racks
innovative includitur modularis tectum quatit
mr. musk has said on Twitter that the
Dominus. dixit quod MOSCHUS on Twitter
recent cyber truck is so planar is that
ita rectilineum salsissimus vir vivens cyber recens est
it can't stamp ultra hard 30 times steel
quod non potest ultra laborare XXX temporibus ferro percutiatur
because it breaks the stamping press
quia torcular calcavit rumpit
despite the initial social media storm
non obstante initial socialis media tempestate
on people mocking the trucks design
consilium populo insultantibus aliquet
others had praised the cyber track for
et laudavit eum in aliis cyber semita
bringing something new to the table wise
est aliquid novum ad mensam sapientes
cam owners will soon find an update
cam dominis cito invenire an update
removes the AI driven person detection
A. homo removeat repulsi deprehendatur
from their device due to the unexpected
propter inopinatum ex fabrica
termination of the agreement Waze had
terminum habens pactum Waze
with their AI provider in waze's
cum A. in waze in provisor est scriptor
commitment wise wise oh my gosh
O mi sapiens sapienti commitment gosh
meatball ways for free they're stating
meatball ipsi erant 'via pro gratis loqui
that their own AI division to bring back
AI divisione sua referre
person direction and other AI
qui ducit et Ai
improvements to the motion detection
improvements in motu deprehensio
wise is being praised by its users on
sapiens dicit, laudari a users in suum
social media for their transparency
socialis instrumentis ad ipsas particulas
though what is not the what is no doubt
quamvis non sit dubium
a difficult situation for their staff
in arto sitos adflictus est in virgam
the new firmware which removes the AI
firmware nova, quae est privatio intellegentiae artificialis
features is planned for mid-january 2020
ora pro cogitavit hoc medium Ianuarii MMXX
there's no ETA yet as to when their new
sed cum illis ut illic 'sine nova ETA
in-house solution will be ready let's
in-domus parata puncto s, erit solution
get into the top stories we're following
ut in summo fabulas his nos erant '
this week the Department of Defense is
hac hebdomada de Department Defensionis est
joining the fight against 5g citing
joining pugna contra deinceps 5g
risks to GPS and military operations the
GPS et ad periculum res est militare
issue is with a proposal before the
exitus est, cum ad rogationem antequam
Federal Communications Commission to
Ad Federal Communicationibus Commissionis
open the 1 to 2 gigahertz frequency
aperire I ad II gigahertz frequency
range the L band for use in 5g cellular
range de L ad cohortem, in usum 5g cellular
networks the problem is that some of
quaestionem, quod quidam networks
those frequencies are already in use by
qui frequentiis in a iam in usum inductorum
the global positioning system and other
in global positioning system et alia
military systems in a letter to FCC
militum systems per epistolam FCC
Chairman a edgy PI Secretary of Defense
Praeses et Secretarius defensionis pendens ex prima hujus
Mark Esper pressed for the rejection of
Mark Fabricius pressed per rejectionem
the proposal saying quote there are too
ex auctoritate dicentis illic es quoque quote
many unknowns and the risks are far too
multa sunt nimis indeterminata et metus
great to federal operations to allow the
magna diam operationes paterentur
proposed system to proceed this could
rogationem procedere ratio potuit
have a significant negative impact on
habet a significant negative ictum
military operations both in peacetime
armisque in pace
and war end quote
et belli finem quote
while supporters of the proposal asite
dum de ea placere sententia rogationem asite
the low power of the transmitters and
humilitatem et potestas transmitters
say this
id
not cause interference studies performed
non studiis peractis causa intercessiones
in 2011 show that GPS signals arriving
pervenientis annuit ostendit MMXI in GPS
from space could be overpowered by even
opprimi posse etiam spatio
low powered ground-based transmissions
Lorem fundatur nuntii humum low-
thanks to the inverse-square law a
gratias reciproca duplicata, ad quadratum lege
report from the National space-based
referunt de National spatium-fundatur
positioning and navigation and timing
positioning et leo et navigation
systems engineering forum noted that the
forum attendendum quod systems engineering
tests demonstrated that there are
quae sunt tests demonstrandum
significantly detrimental impacts to all
confligant omnia detrimentum esse significantly
GPS applications assessed and quote
GPS applications et taxantur quote
could it be that we're like approaching
potest fieri, ut sis quasi appropinquanti
that time when there just aren't enough
si parum est quod
frequencies left like do you think that
putas frequentiis derelinquetur
we're almost there yeah it sounds like
erant 'non fere ita sonat yeah
we're there they're using frequencies
erant autem ibi erant 'usura frequentiis
that are already in use are there more
quae sunt plures iam in usum inductorum
frequencies we can just tap into let's
frequentiis nos iustus ICTUS in puncto s
jump into the 50 gigahertz band and see
L gigahertz cohortem et salire ad videre
what it does to our brains like that's
quod non est simile, quae in cerebro
the thing all right it's safe we've had
omne ius rei suus 'tutum weve' had
Wi-Fi interviews covering in the past
Wi-FI colloquiis covering in praeteritis
how they want to split up the way that
quo volunt hoc modo secantur,
they're doing Wi-Fi in the home so it
sic discis Wi-FI est in domum suam
makes me wonder if there's a way to take
Miror, si illic 'a via ad me
some of these bands and kind of do the
et in vinculis non modo ex
same deal you know because it was I
idem paciscor ut scitis quod factum est
forget what the technology was called
quid esset oblivisci technology vocavit
but it was an innovative new approach
sed nova amet
that basically was kind of like you know
scis quia amo genus plerumque
adding more lanes to a highway when it
in via quando vicos additis
comes to Wi-Fi and so I wonder if
et venit ad Wi-FI Nescio,
something like that could add more bands
quid ultra addere potest quod quasi vincula
without necessarily boosting to a higher
esse sine superiori boosting
power but you still need in order to
sed adhuc opus est ut potentia
have more bands if you will using your
Si autem plura vincula et arca tua
term it's you need more frequencies
suus 'ultra terminum opus frequentiis
right so but if they put things on I
Ego autem si rebus Habemus
think what the issue here is the
Quid putas hic est exitus
misconception that terrestrial low
deceptae terrestria deorsum
powered broadcast will not interfere
Lorem non passim intermixti
with the big powerful satellites that
quae cum magna fortitudine satellites
have really powerful broadcast well
passim etiam in potentia realiter
thanks to the inverse-square exactly
gratias agere prorsus inversus-quadratus
anybody who has ever done karaoke knows
aliorum qui novit unquam fieri Magnificat &amp; Nunc Dimittis
that if you take the left and right
Quod si dextra
channel and invert one of them and
et Portae ex alveo
overlap them you get a mono signal and
aliudque eis signum, et vos adepto a mono
it takes the vocals out well how does
et quoque quod vocales quomodo non capit
that happen it happens because typically
quoniam saepe contingit accidere
vocals are in the middle so it by in
ita in medio juxta Vocales
inverting your phasing out the middle
de medio tui invertendo phasing
channels
channels
similarily you're gonna get an like that
similarily te agnus dei adepto, quod est quasi
kind of effect where two overlapping
genus effectus duo imbricatis
signals you're going to cause
annuit vos erant 'iens ut causam
interference that is going to actually
intercessiones, quod est iens actually
phase out certain portions of that
et quasdam frugum illius
signal and I think that's the concern
et cogitant de signo ut '
that has been brought forward but of
sed de illis quae allata sunt
course those who are creating the low
Nimirum desunt qui humilitatem
powered terrestrial signals are saying
annuit autem dicere ad terrestres veniamus powered
oh no these are just low powered signals
Immo haec signa sunt humiles Lorem
it's not going to cause any problem but
sed suus 'forsit non iens ut aliqua de causa
meanwhile yeah there's a very real
yeah interim verus illic 'a valde
chance that it could so I wonder what
Miror quod sic forte quod esset
the solution would be I would think that
solution ad hoc esset ut videtur
the military should probably have a
est verisimile have a militum ut
frequency that couldn't be like the alb
alba sicut posse frequentia
and well the thing is they've they've
bene res habent et non habent
been using their own band but that but
sed quod non est per se cohortem
the issue I think is that I mean I'm
exitus puto autem quod Im 'mean
speculating because I'm not on the inner
quia speculando non sum in interiorem
circle of the US military obviously I
et manifesto in circulo US
can't even get a meatball right but the
sed etiam non adepto a dextris meatball
thing is the military has always been
quae semper est rei bellicae est
ahead of the curve when it comes to
praemisit, &amp; ipsius curvae cum fit,
technology yes and it makes me wonder if
et quod sic technology magis miror, si
we've kind of hit this period in in our
Ive 'hoc genus in tempus hac nostra hit
world where technology is starting to
ubi est incipiens ad technology mundi
advance faster than what the military
militum quam doleo
can advance and so the issue they're
ita haerent eventu itineris
running into is that society's catching
currens est in societatem capit est scriptor
up right and so is it possible that
Unde recte fieri
we're reaching a point I mean not even
ne quidem puncto sit a me erant reaching
just about a signal but that in general
qui autem iustus de signo in communi,
the world has started to nip at the
orbis terrarum has coepi ut ad nip
heels of military advancement because of
propter augmentum militarium in passibus suis comitatur
so many companies and so many smart
tot et tot societates dolor
people out there doing crazy things
nulla res agere populum insanum
under personal Enterprise that the
ut in personale Enterprise
military is going can we keep up right
militum custodire eum est iens possumus recte
and what does this mean yeah I kind of
Et hoc est quod quidam Yeah
stay ahead of that curve then they say
dico igitur quod praemisit sede huius curuae spectanda
okay no more 5g really to 233 computers
5g realiter est bene ultra CCXXXIII computers
because that's I mean that's the only
quod id non sit nisi quam suus
thing they can do right now it really
nunc autem rem facere non possum realiter
would mess with their safety right their
Utinam jus suum saluti tatam
security and well I mean look at I'm
nee sum animi securitate et in medium Im 'vultus
gonna say was a couple years ago we had
agnus dei dicat esse in duobus abhinc annis habuimus
that whole GPS issue where people were
qua re omnem populum GPS
using their Fitbit at secret military
militum ad occultas suas Fitbit
base and it was pointing up on a map
basi in tabula designasse
yeah because they're walking around like
yeah quia erant sicut circum ambulant
techno
techno
she has reached the point where we're
se habet ad hoc usque pervenit sumus
going what kind of other implications
alterum habet exitum qualem
are we not paying attention to that just
non attendentes quod sicut nobis non est
seems so benign but really is a big
quam benigna, sed vere videtur esse a magnus
concern and this is one where the
et haec est de qua
military may actually have a very legit
militare, ut ipso actu a legit
concern going this could be a national
de eo quod posset esse nationalis
security risk if we have you know
habet securitatem periculo, si non scitis
special signals that get intercepted by
qui annuit specialis adepto circumuentum ab regiis
Joe Blow with his you know low frequency
Canite Joe frequentia sua vestrum cognoscere
stuff at home it's very true I don't
supellectilem domi suus 'verum non faciam
know I don't even I don't know how to
non sciunt, ne quidem nescio quam
properly answer the concern to be honest
recte respondendum de honestus esse
I don't either but it's an interesting
Sed nec illud facio amet
story to follow for her mm-hmm
fabulam pro ea sequi-mm hmm
Google is serious about ensuring the
De gravi cursus ad Google
pixel line of Android phones is secure
Android risus linea firmatam pixel
they've announced that they'll pay
theyve 'millia talentorum appendam arcariis nuntiatum est illi
security researchers up to 1.5 million
Inquisitores securitas usque ad 1.5 decies centena
dollars to find hacks and exploits the
dollars invenire auto rebus gestis suum
company said Thursday that effective
Dixit turba Iovis, quod effective
immediately they'll pay 1 million
protinus ad I decies centena millia talentorum appendam arcariis
dollars for a quote full chain remote
full quote pupa torquem remote
code execution exploit with persistence
codice facinoris mortem permaneat
which compromises the Titan M secure
Titan, qui in discrimen adducat ad M secure
element on pixel devices and quote
et cogitationes elementum pixel in quote
they'll also pay $500,000 for exploits
quod youll 'quoque reddere $ 500,000 rebus gestis amplissimus
that covertly steal data from a pixel or
quæ data clam furantur, aut ex pixel
bypass its lock screen Google will offer
suum offeret Bypass tincidunt elit Google
a 50% bonus to any of its rewards if the
% L in punctis salutis in aliqua sui propositis praemiis,
exploit works on specific Developer
in propria opera et facta Developer
Preview versions of Android that means a
Significat quod a preview of Android versiones
critical Titan M hack on a Developer
M discrimine Titan obvium saginantur in Developer
Preview could fetch 1.5 million dollars
Preview 1.5 million pupa potest arcessere
and a data exfiltration or lock screen
et clausum, et data screen exfiltration
bypass could earn 750 thousand dollars
DCCL centena acquirere potuit Bypass
and so on previously rewards for the
ita prius praemia
most severe Android exploits topped out
transcendi de rebus gravissimis MASCULINUS
at $200,000 the big reward bump
$ 200,000 ad praemium magna gibba
coincides with the investments Google
coincidit cum investments Google
has poured into securing the pixel the
quae infudit in securitate in pixel
Titan M is a Google designed chip that's
M Titan obvium est ut chip a Google scriptor disposito
physically segregated from the main
natura disiungitur ab alto
chipset of the device Titan M was first
cor versa est in prima M Titan obvium fabrica
introduced in 2018 with the rollout of
introduced in MMXVIII cum a rollout
the pixel 3 it's also in the recently
suus etiam nuper in III pixel
released pixel 3a and will also be
3 * Et erit et dimisit pixel
included in the just-released pixel for
sicut includitur in pixel in dimisit,
security researcher Salim Rashid
securitatem indagator Salim Rashid
suspects were in the midst of an iOS
iOS suspicatur in medio
Android security paradigm shift
Android securitatem tangibilem
to understand the significance of
ut intellegere
Google's announcement third party
Googles ope apud tertia pars denuntiatio
exploit brokers 0 diem will pay hackers
0 diem poenas non credam praesidium sectorum existimetur Forum
$100,000 to weaponize a lockscreen
$ 100,000 in cincinno-in weaponize
bypass on either iOS or Android Google
iOS et Android Bypass vel Google
are offering up to seven and a half
ad propria voluntate et dimidium septem
times as much Wow so that's that's
Curabitur id est et septies tantum
really just smart thinking really
vere cogitandi vere iustus dolor
because it's worth the money to pay to
quia dignum est ut pecuniam reddere
make sure that there isn't going to be
efficere futurum quod non
an exploit by somebody malicious you
quis ex facinus videre, perverse Menalca
great you just really want to be I guess
Ego coniecto vos iustus volo ut rem magnam
you want to be enticing enough that
satis est ut vis sollicitans
nobody's going to pay more for the
nullus suus 'iens magis stipendium ad
exploit right and what you yeah and you
Gaudete et facias tibi ius
may as well use it for good right if if
potest etiam uti nisi ad dextera, si bona
someone's gonna hack the operating
suus 'agnus dei aliquis trucidabunt operating
system of an android device a pixel
systema quod Android fabrica a pixel
device may as well give them enough
consilium dare possit quam parum
incentive that instead of selling that
excitat, quae est pro venditionis
to the bad guys yes sell it directly to
in malum guys etiam vendere directe ad eam
Google so that they can fix it and
Google reficere possint et
you're gonna get seven and a half times
vestri 'agnus dei adepto septem et dimidium temporis
right I would do it for good and also
ut iustum et bonum faciam
for $750,000 no I mean this sounds
Ego enim non intelliguntur hic sonitus $ 750,000
self-serving I mean not for myself
servientes sui, ut sit ipse non
because I have no clue how to even go
quod etiam have no clue quo vado
down that road I am NOT a hacker cracker
quia ego sum via et a Piratica non cracker
at all but this seems like as a
sed omnino videtur quasi
potential self-serving problem for
potential forsit per sui, servientes
somebody who goes I found the exploit
qui aliquo negotio inveni
yeah I found the problem Google I
yeah non inveni quaestio Google
realize you're offering 1.5 million but
1.5 million, sed animadverto dicas offerent
I can sell it on the black market for 4
Non possum vendere eam in nigrum foro ut IV
million but they can't they cannot
sed decies potest non possunt
that's the thing they can sell it for a
eo quod non possunt vendere pro
hundred thousand so Google sang will
Voluntas igitur carmen milia Google
give you seven and a half times that
tibi septem tempora et dimidium temporis
exactly Google is totally out bidding
prorsus iussa sunt prorsus Google
the highest bidder of any I I understand
II intelligere quod aliquid debetur inemptis
that but I mean as we keep bumping these
sed quae sit ut haec custodias bumping
prices up people are gonna recognize oh
O agnoscis prices sursum sunt agnus
if I find that one exploit it's gonna be
EGO reperio ut suus 'agnus dei esse nisi unum caeloque Ereboque
a massive payday and I'm not happy with
Non est beatus, cum ingenti mole me et payday
1.5 like right now we're in 1.5 how long
1.5 ut 1.5 nunc sumus in quousque
before we're gonna see a three or a ten
ut ante amet video aut decem tribus
or a 25 million dollar payout for an
XXV million pupa vel quia est exsolvere
exploit to be identified because I mean
identified quod sit ut credam
you have to ask yourself how much money
Habes tantam pecuniam, quam ut Ipse te interroga,
is Google gonna make in putting out
Google exstinctis amet facere
these phones and you know is somebody
quia haec phones et quis est,
gonna look and be like yeah it's not
O Yeah respiciens tamquam suus
good enough like this does this just you
Hoc satis est iustus non est similis tui
know read some selfishness I don't know
alii legere scis nimium nescio
no no I feel like it's such a good pail
non sentio amo suus 'non bonum ut protinus deunces,
like it's such an amazing reward but I
Mirum est pretium sed talem qualis
think that people will actually up their
Puto autem quod usque in actually
game trying to find it turns into
vertit illud in ludum conatur invenire
lecture it turns into trying to find an
disputare an illo vertit in quaerit inveniet
easter egg in Oh some movie that I can't
O Pascha ovum in aliquam elit ut possunt
remember right now there's Easter eggs
Nunc autem meminisse fas illic 'Ova paschae
in a whole bunch more yes okay but it
Etiam purus nibh, sed potius toti
will make people try harder to actually
magis populus tendo ut ipse faciet
find the exploit making the exploits
invenire res facias violentiam faciens
obvious faster making it more secure
citius magis obvious facit secure
quicker and then there won't be the
citius enim non esse et
option of selling anything to the the
in facultate vendere aliquid ex
dirt I think that's the answer right so
ius responsum ut lutum puto ut '
nobody's gonna be like can I have 751 if
ut nullus suus 'agnus dei esse non possum, si DCCLI
there's anything that we know like from
illic 'aliquid cognoscatur a nobis quasi ex
the whole marketplace of let's say
totum forum lets 'narro
ransomware just using the example what
in exemplum iusti, quae per Ransomware
do we know about hackers due to
De hoc scimus ex hackers
ransomware they want a quick payday
Ransomware quod volo a velox payday
right so if I'm a hacker and I'm not but
si ergo recte, et non sum, sed ego a Piratica
if I was and I found this exploit and
Si inveni erat, et hanc facias, et
was able to create an exploit for the
creare poterat ad facinus videre
pixel I'm going to want what a quick
Im 'iens ut volo a velox quod ego pixel
payday so am I gonna go to the guys that
Thursday, ut ego vadam ad guys ut agnus
are giving me $100,000 or am I gonna go
sunt praecipio non ego sum agnus dei ite mecum $ 100,000
to the ones that are paying me seven
et quod ones es mihi septem solvente
hundred and fifty thousand dollars you
et quinquaginta milia pupa
know what the answer to that is that is
quid est, quod est responsum, quod ad
the idea behind what Google is doing I
ratio facit et dimittit Google
suspect and I think that it's a really
Puto autem quod suus 'vere et suspicaturus
good motivator for for I'll say a
Et dices ad bonum enim est motivator
motivator a lot of times what we
quod multum temporis Motivator
perceive as a bad guy in the hacking
sentiet mala in caesim amet
industry will call it is really just
vocatis autem industria est tantum realiter
somebody that it has fallen upon the
quis non cecidit super eam
wrong channel okay if I find this hack
EGO reperio is hack alienum deerraverit tramitem, si bene
oh I can sell it for a hundred thousand
Quis possum vendere centum milia
dollars so if that's my option now I've
nunc igitur si, quae mihi optio dollars quia commune aut inmundum
got this opportunity to get a hundred
nactus occasionem accipiat centies
thousand dollars right and and it's not
quod jus non centena
necessarily that they are a bad person
oportet esse malus
or that they are doing a bad thing is
aut non faciant mali
just well but now it's been weaponized
sicut etiam nunc suus 'been weaponized
because the the that group has bought it
quia in hoc coetus est emit eam
so what they're doing is they're also
Quid est quod tu et discis
reallocating
reallocating
the brilliant minds of the youth and the
animos adulescentium et praeclara
the hacker the hackers and really
in Piratica per hackers et realiter
redirecting that toward correcting the
quod in corrigendo redirecting
situation and saying okay we'll give you
et rei bene nobis dicens non do tibi
more money and and you're gonna you're
tu es et pecuniam amet
helping to improve the security of the
de securitate ad auxilium amplio
platform right so I think it's a whole
Habemus diam Puto totum
it does so much good I agree I think
et non tantum bonis Ego assentior
they should also offer them a job to be
sed etiam ad officium offerre
honest and that that could happen yeah
Yeah quod honestum fieri
Microsoft used to do that years ago when
Microsoft facere solebat, ut, cum annos
they first set up their website it was
primum instaurata fuit website
it can happen multiple layers of
stratis contingit multipliciter
security like if you break in you get a
sicut si pignus a conteram in vobis
job here I feel like this whole story is
res tota vilicatione sentiant
something that like would inspire Amy
inspire quasi Amy quod aliquid esset,
didi
didi
right like she'd be like yeah I'm all
illa youd 'amo iustum esse sicut me omnes yeah
over this we've got to take a quick
Comperto ad a velox super hoc
break the crypto report and more of this
et huius fama praevaricator Crypto
week's top tech stories are coming up
tech septimana scriptor summo ecce venient in fabulis
don't go anywhere
Non ivit servus tuus quoquam
[Music]
[Musica]
welcome
gratissimum
a quick look at the crypto report and
a velox vultus ad fama et Crypto
how things look as of Wednesday November
November quae spectant quam sicut de Mercurii
27th 2019 via our website category 5 dot
27 MMXIX nostris per website V dat genus
TV we've been collecting the data and
Ive 'been colligendis hoc notitia, et in TV
looking at how things have been
At quaeris quomodo res fuerunt
transitioning over the past week and
transitioning, et per hebdomadam revolutam
we're seeing that Bitcoin is really
BitCoin erant cum eo est realiter
losing a fair bit this week dropping
amissis septem enim distillans labia est modicum iusto
down more than $1,000 us as far as its
descendit plus quam $ 1,000 pro nobis usque ad
US dollar equivalent value down at seven
In equivalent US pupa in valorem septem
thousand one hundred and ninety three
tria milia ducenti nonaginta
dollars and change
et mutatio dollars
litecoin is also down I mean everything
Ego quoque in medium quae litecoin
is on is on the decline this week at 46
in hoc quod declines a septimana a XLVI
dollars and 87 cents aetherium
LXXXVII dollars et cents aetherium
is at 147 eighty-one Manero is down at
CXLVII est ad esse octoginta Manero
5150 for not dropping as much as I would
(V)CL non cadunt ut quod vellet
have expected considering the exploit
pro facinus speraret
that happened on their website this week
factum est autem in hac septimana website
turtle coin is holding fairly steady
testudo graeca aes tenens iuste stabilis
having dropped just 0.01 ten thousandth
cecidit autem iustus 0.01 unam myriadis
of a cent to 0.23 and we're now looking
0.23 et respiciens ad nos nunc de cent
at the basic attention token as well and
et ad prima ac diligentia tulerunt
that is down from last week at zero
id est ab ultima septimana ad nulla
well 21 cents US per coin remember that
XXI cents per US bene memini quae numerata
this is not we're not providing any kind
id est non erant 'non aliqua providing
of financial advice or investment advice
neque consilium a financial investment consilium
what we are giving you is just the facts
quae res est quae tibi
with regards to cryptocurrency and the
et penes cryptocurrency
different coins that we are monitoring
denarios diversis, ut sunt vigilantia
here at the studio the cryptocurrency
hic ad studio in cryptocurrency
market never closes
clauserit viscera nunquam forum
and it's always volatile so make sure
et sic suus 'semper fac volatile
that you only invest what you are able
quod non potest investimus quod es
and willing to lose because it's quite
quod plane volens perdere
probable that you may never turn in an
ut numquam veri simile quod per vertere
income from it and that's not our intent
Et post reditum ab intentionis
we just want to give you the facts you
si vis dare factis
can find out more at category-five dot
e pluribus invenire a quinque-genus dot
TV click on shows the category-five TV
Genus-click in TV ostendit quinque TV
newsroom and you'll see the crypto
newsroom quod youll 'animadverto in Crypto
report there and that will just give you
et non referunt qui tantum dabit vobis
up to up to the day cryptocurrency data
usque ad diem data cryptocurrency
for the coins that we are tracking I'm
denarios ad me ut sint tracking
gonna head back over the newsroom to you
O vos capitis trans Newsroom
two
duabus
Thank You Ravi the official site for the
Tibi gratias ago ravi in ​​te situm est officialis
Monaro digital coin was hacked to
Digital Monaro numerata pecunia est caederetur ruebat
deliver currency stealing malware to you
monetæ eripere furtum est et malware
speaking up we're downloading a wallet
loquebatur autem erant etiam peram downloads
software mm-hmm yep the supply chain
hmm yep in copia catena mm-software
attack came to light last week
luminis impetus ad ultima septimana
Monday when a site user reported that
Cum Lunae locum a user referunt
the cryptographic hash for a command
Nullam imperium in cryptographic
line interface wallet downloaded from
linea ab downloaded peram interface
the site didn't match the hash listed on
Nullam in locum nullum vinculum inscripti
the page over the next several hours
page horas in posterum
users discovered that the mismatching
users inventa est mismatching
hash wasn't the result of an error
Nullam non est effectus errorem
instead it was an attack designed to
sed impetum eius intentio
infect get Manero users with malware
inficiat adepto users with malware Manero
site officials later confirmed that
postea confirmavit locum magistratus
finding an analysis of the malicious
per analysis invenire malitiosorum
Linux binary found that it added a few
Addidit pauca inveni binarii linux
new functions to the legitimate one one
legitimate unum novum munera ad unum
of the functions was called after user
cum dicitur de user est munera
opened or created a new wallet it sent
neque peram suam aperuit novum misit illum
the wallet seed which is the
qui sit vidulus semen
cryptographic secret key used to access
secretum accessum ad key cryptographic
wallet funds to a third party server the
in peram pecunia est tertia pars servo
malware then sent wallet funds to
et malware peram pecunia missum est
another server at least one person
alius homo servo saltem unus
participating in a reddit forum claimed
participating in a foro petita reddit
to have lost digital coins after
pereunt enim in digital post nummos
installing the malicious Linux binary a
installing binarii ad occidendum alterutrum paratiores erunt Linux
malicious Windows version of the CLI
malicious Fenestra poema in cli
wallet carried out an almost identical
peram transtulerint fere
attack sequence anyone who downloaded
quis ordo, qui impetum downloaded
the CLI Manero wallet on Monday November
manticae quid in cli Lunae November Manero
2019 is advised to check the hashes of
MMXIX est consilium reprehendo in ad de hashes
their binaries if they don't match the
et si non par binaries
official ones delete the files and
et delete lima ones officialis
download them again do not run
et iterum download non decurrunt,
compromised binaries for any reason I
aliqua ratione suspectus binaries
think yeah and this just goes to show
Puto justo id ipsum ostendit Yeah
like if there is a checksum difference
ut si a sit checksum
so if you've got the md5 or the sha
et si ego in md5 aut sha
checksum and it doesn't match what it's
Et quid suus 'non congruit checksum
supposed to be just don't even touch it
et ne tangeremus illud putatur iustus
just like find out what's going on
invenimus quod suus 'iens sicut ex supra
because you may think hey well that's
quia potest cogitare quod bene heus est scriptor
weird it doesn't match well in this
tam infandum, quod non congruit hoc
particular case it could have saved like
casu ut salvos fieri
the one that I heard of like lost $7,000
unum hoc audivi quasi perdidit ex $ 7.000
out of their wallet as far as US
de pera sua usque ad US
currency goes and it just you know you
sicut mos est et scitis
got to be careful and crypto currency is
et surrexit ut caveat monetæ est Crypto
a really really lucrative target for
nam vere et realiter sumptus lucrosce scopum
malicious attackers and it can happen it
et hoc contingit malitiosi oppugnatores
can happen and in this case hey you have
Heus tu hoc fieri potest
to be really diligent I mean it would be
ut non sit diligentius hoc esset
it would be so simple just to assume
Iustus ut simplex esset assumere,
that everything was going right except
sed omnia recte agerentur
here here you go and the half
Hic hic te, et dimidium
just don't watch out yeah well exactly
vigilate, iusti, non de tam exacte yeah
and I mean I know that there's different
et illic 'aliud quod sit novi
type of wallets you can use like you can
Vos can utor of wallets typus ut vos can
use your cloud-based wallet you can have
nubes-ut vos can utor vestri pera fundatur
a software wallet you can have a paper
paper pera potes habere a software
wallet that's completely cut off from
exterminabitur de s vidulus
the world but I mean each of them comes
sed intelliguntur per orbem terrarum ex illis est
with their own risks I mean and if
Et si medium et cum suis metus
you're gonna go with a paper wallet
es agnus dei ire cum charta peram suam
because you're like hey I don't want to
quia erant sicut heus non vis
be caught by something like this if you
si tale capiendus
ever lose your paper you're toast right
tua paper semper carere es tu iure aemulantur tosti
you know and it's unfortunate I mean as
et quod medium est, et scitis infortunatus
somebody who is mined mineiro in the
quis est qui fodit in mineiro
past you know it's so easy to just kind
iam scis ut quaedam tam facile
of like oh here's you know another wall
Quis similis tibi hic paries
I'm gonna try this sure and you're not
Im 'agnus dei, et haec tempta, cave ne te
even paying attention and then you hit
et vos igitur attendentes quod ledo
your minor and away you go
et auferetur tua minor te,
you know and you walk away and then
et tu scis et discedere
comeback days later to see how you're
REGRESSUS post dies quam ad te
doing and in that meantime you've lost
interea, quod facio et te perdidit
everything because you're not paying
omne quod tibi non solvente
attention and it's so easy to do Jeff
Jeff curam suus facile
I've even heard of people that will set
Ego autem populus audivit et non liberabit
up automatic updates for their wallet
Lorem et peram updates
software and their mining software and
et metalla et software software
when you do that and it's it's tough
Dum suus et facere suus 'lenta
because a lot of times like scale is a
Multum est quod interdum eu
perfect example where the coin has
exempli gratia, ubi est perfecta denarios
changed so many times that it just gets
ita fit ut saepe mutatur
frustrating because you've got to keep
quia tu obtinuit ut frustrating
reinstalling the software so people will
reinstalling ad populum et erit software
tend to set up an automatic updater and
tendit et constituere dui updater
what happens if that update comes down
Quid si venerit renovatio
the wire and it's malicious that's a big
et quod suus 'a magnus filum malicious
problem and when it comes to
forsit quod cum fit,
cryptocurrency
cryptocurrency
there's there's really no way to get
Ibi suus 'illic' realiter nullo modo ut
your money back was gone it's no it's
Nulla erat enim illud nummos
not like it's a regulated financial
ut suus 'non a financial instituta
transaction where you know you can buy
qua re tu scis te potest emere
insurance on it right it's not insured
suus 'non securus de nullo iure assecurationis in ea
in any way it's scary that this is
ullo modo est ut suus 'FORMIDULOSUS
happening so I feel like early in the
sic fieri placet in mane
life of cryptocurrency but I know it's
Scio suus 'non vitam cryptocurrency
not like early early days but I feel
neque sentiunt quasi mane diluculo sed dierum
like it's scary that now as it's
Nunc suus 'FORMIDULOSUS quia amo ut suus'
becoming more common knowledge that
quae magis communia
cryptocurrency exists and people are
cryptocurrency existit et homines
kind of getting right on the bandwagon
genus bandwagon in iustitia
in the malls there are Bitcoin vendors
in malls sunt BitCoin vendentes,
and now this is coming out which makes
et nunc ex quo haec venit facit
me think is this the beginning of a
Puto me hoc principium est: a
cycle that's going to gain momentum and
lucro futurum est cyclus impetu
I wonder whether there is going to be a
Nescio enim an hoc facturus esset
way then to ensure that that's a valid
Sic ergo id est ut validum
concern Sasha yeah
de Not yeah
but I think what it is is it's really
sed putat quod is sit suus 'realiter
just like this is something that's gonna
sicut est aliquid quod suus 'agnus dei
constantly be under attack
continuo impugnatione
so is this gonna be a wake up call
sic dico surge sit amet
Foreman arrows developers for example to
Maecenas sagittis puta ignarum
solidify their security something went
quod securitas ad solidatur sua
wrong
malum
something allowed this to happen they'll
licet hoc fit aliquid quod tibi placet
need to figure out what happened and put
opus et factum est ut instar sicco quod implebis
a stop to it and and protect their users
et tuentur et finem users
plain and simple it makes me wonder I
Ego simplex, et patet quod magis miror
mean because you already have the US
Iam quod vult US
government looking at regulatory
in regulatory regimen quaeritis
oversight and declaring liebre from
inspectionem praediti nuntiantes in dignitate a liebre
Facebook right as a securities currency
Facebook rectum in monetæ agmen traduceret,
it makes me wonder if this is gonna open
eo magis miror, si id apertum sit amet
the door because the issues we've that
quod inest rebus, quae nobis ianuam
have gone around the globe with Bitcoin
et abiit circum orbem BitCoin
and now you've got this issue with
surrexit ergo et tu cum hic exitus
monaro if it's going to start pushing
Si suus 'iens ut satus monaro cornibus
regulatory oversight in legislation that
per inspectionem et leges regulatory
says you know what cryptocurrencies are
Dicit enim scitis quod cryptocurrencies
in fact a financial transaction they
pecuniaria quidem de re gesta sunt,
should be governed by the navvies
debeant gubernari navvies
Commission I don't fear that no but it
Non vereor ne non illud Commission
makes you it does make me wonder if it's
quod non facit facere miror si suus '
gonna get to the point where somebody's
ubi 'agnus dei adepto in punctum aliquem scriptor
gonna bring that topic up and say this
ac deducere eum locum, id est agnus
needs to happen now they're just gonna
Necesse est autem quod fit iustus amet
say too bad so sad it's not a valid
Dicunt etiam quod tristem, ita malum non est verum
currency that's how they'll move on yeah
pecuniam quam Venerem quod memini proficiscantur
and speaking of Sasha we're gonna jump
et loquebatur de Not sumus agnus dei jump
into the next story wouldn't it be nice
Aliquam eu est nec in alteram
if there was a facebook rival well there
si non erat bene aemulus facebook
is and it's founded by the guy who built
et factum est condita suus 'a guy qui fabricavit illam
Wikipedia Jimmy Wales is expressing
Jimmy Wales varius id est expressing
excitement that his new social network
trepidique ut nova socialis network
WT social already has more than 160,000
WT socialis iam magis quam 160,000
members the platform says it will never
platform autem membra non dicit
sell user data and relies on the
Et placebit vecordia sua user notitia est vendere
generosity of individual donors rather
magis liberalitate singula donatorum
than ads the donations are by way of a
quam ads in enim a modo de donations
modest subscription fee it is
quod est subscriptio feodo verecundus
positioning itself as news focused place
positioning et ipsum focused in loco nuntium
and says members will be able to edit
inquit membra poterit recensere
misleading headlines they will see the
subvertentem gentem headlines non videbis
articles shared by their network in a
retiacula in commune vasorum suorum
timeline format appearing with the
cum forma apparere timeline
newest first rather than algorithms that
novissima algorithms ut quam primum
try to appeal to their interests the
appellatio capto enim utilitatis
introduction to WT social says quote we
WT socialis introductio ad hoc dicit quote
will empower you to make your own
voluntas tua, ut do facultatem,
choices about what content you are
quae circa electiones contentus es,
served and to directly edit misleading
et servivit directe subvertentem gentem recensere
headlines or flag problem posts we will
headlines vel vexillum volumus forsit stipes
foster an environment where bad actor
vbi nulla fovere pessimo histrione
removed because it is right not because
quia non oportet auferri
it suddenly affects our bottom-line
imo statim tangit lineam
unquote
Unquote
in a recent interview with the Financial
in colloquium cum recens Financial
Times mr. Wales shared his view that the
Tempora metus. Wallia communicato opinantibus
problem with advertising led services
Difficultas vendo servicia ducitur
such as Facebook is that the winners
quod sit sicut Facebook winners
often low quality content social media
plerumque humilis qualis contentus socialis instrumentis
consult the consultant Zoe Carnes said
Carnes consule dicitur consultant Zoes
that she thought the network would have
quia putavit se habent ad network
to grow its numbers quickly in order to
celeriter crescunt ut plures
prove itself to be an a viable
probare ipsum esse est a viable
alternative to the Giants she says quote
Gigantes autem modo illa dicit quote
it's going to need a lot of money plowed
suus 'iens ut postulo multus of pecuniam scidit vomere
into it people are so used to social
ut in ea homines ad socialis
media being free I think businesses
media esse liberi puto businesses
might pay for it but people are so used
sed et homines, ut solebat reddere pro eo
to having news at their fingertips for
Ad nuntium ad eorum fingertips enim habens
free end quote
liberum finem quote
WT social is a separate entity to
WT socialis est separatum est
Wikipedia and can be found at WT dot
Wikipedia potest inveniri ad apicem WT
social this is an interesting one I
Hoc est interesting et socialis unum
would say that this is something I'm not
Im 'non dicat quod sit aliquid
necessarily something that I'm going to
necessario aliquid quod Im 'iens
immediately delve into but I like the
sed statim ut altius erit
idea of paying for the idea that my
ideam de solvente ad ideam meam
stuff is never gonna be sold like if I
ut non vendetur si sit amet supellectilem
think you're not going to be from the
Non puto te erant 'iens futurus a
sound of it you're not gonna be
quod sonus non es agnus
manipulated right by what is making them
quod facere jure regantur
money exactly now the tricky part about
iam plane de parte pecuniae amet
it is a little bit like in the back of
in posteriore simile est exigua,
my mind I think Wikipedia isn't like a
animus puto, non quasi Vicipaedia
super reliable source when you're doing
Super authoremque sectari tibi discis
research but this isn't about research
sed hoc non est de investigationis quaerere
this is about entertaining news stories
quod sumptum est de nuntium fabulas
social media yeah I see I wonder though
Nescio, quamquam video socialis instrumentis yeah
like I get what they're going for and
sicut et ego quia et id quod ipsi erant 'iens
and I get the whole subscription-based
et adepto totus subscriptionis fundatur,
thing whatever that modest fee might be
modesta pretium quodcumque sit illud
I don't know if it's something I will
Quod ego nescio si suus '
but would you pay 14 now see I don't
XIV redde tu autem iam non ego video
think I would because once they get you
Et puto, quia si statim ad te
hooked then the fees go up because oh
Quia igitur o militum ascendat aduncis
it's more expensive we've had it Wow
illud quod est magis pretiosa diximus Wow
Jeff is like all over like as soon as
Simile est cum omni Schola
you give them five dollars it'll be ten
quinquies decies centena des itll
dollars okay that's the way that Netflix
ut pupa ut 'okay Netflix
was that I mean as they keep pushing on
est quia intelliguntur illi servo quantum in propellentibus
new content which I'm not knocking
Novum contentus quæ ego non pulsate
Netflix but I mean you get locked in at
Sed non vult adepto clausum in a Netflix
$7.99 what was a ten years ago and now
$ 7.99 per decem annos, et quod nunc
you're looking at $14.99 like the price
ut pretium at $ 14.99 quaeritis
is doubled and you're still getting the
Erant tamen questus quod et tu Secundi: Historia Naturalis
same server
eadem server
is just extra content they're producing
qui erant extra contentus est producendo
more shows but honey that's Netflix the
amplius autem ostendit quod mel de Netflix
whole point with this thing my concern
punctum huic rei de toto meo
though is the fact that it's user edited
etsi sit quod user scriptor edited
input like we already have a problem now
sicut iam nos have a forsit iam initus
with fake news and me--let manipulated
cum fake nuntium et te - fiat manipulated
the opposite of fake news though I
contrarium est quamquam ego nuntium fake
understand that but somebody added sin I
quod aliquem intelligere, sed non addidit peccatum
mean you see this now with Wikipedia I
intelliguntur videtis hanc nunc ego Vicipaedia
mean what was it about for 15 years
Quid enim ad medium fere XV annis
there was a fake religious God that was
erat autem Deum ut religionis fake
on Wikipedia that was deemed to be real
Wikipedia, quod dignatus sit realis,
but in fact it wasn't because somebody
sed quoniam re vera esset, non aliquem
put something on there that wasn't true
pone super aliqua ibi esset, quod non est verum
and never got caught so what's to say
Et quid suus 'nunquam got captus et dicere
you have a news article where somebody
nuntium articulus, ubi quis in vobis
goes hey you know what this is this is a
Nullam id quod sequitur nosti
great article but I think I'm going to
Puto Im 'iens magnus articulus sed
change it just just slightly so that
mutata paulum, ut ea iusta iustum
it's 98% true but there's a little bit
suus 'verum, sed illic' XCVIII% exigua,
of false fact in it and suddenly it
quod falsum est repente quippe
continues to grow and it takes off we
ita crescunt et praecingit nobis
already have this problem now the whole
Tota res iam
idea of having a social medias
habere communem rationem medias
subscription-based service that people
subscribendi servitium, secundum quod
can then edit and alter the news on I
et recensere potes, et mutant nuntium ad me
find wrong but the alternative is a
sed aliud est malum inveniet
social media platform where you don't
amicabiliter interventus suggestus in qua non facis
have the opportunity to edit those who
Qui edit occasionem
have the money control exactly those who
qui pecunias habent prorsus imperium
have who put billions of dollars into it
habere illum qui eripuit innumerabilem pupa
are able to control and edit if you're
Si vestri 'control et redire possunt recensere
given the choice of only two things
daretur arbitrium et duas tantum res
you're given Facebook or WT social
tibi dedi Facebook vel socialis WT
Facebook is free but right but you're
Est autem ius, sed liberum Facebook te
going to be manipulated according to
Ad secundum usurpari
what they think you want to see social
Quid vis videre, cogitant socialis
is going to show you news stories that
Ad nuntium fabulas ut sit tibi
could perhaps be edited by peers so the
in eo consuetudines by a parium suorum et
question becomes then Jeff would you
interrogatio erit si ergo vos Jeff
give WT social a chance by trying it for
WT dare socialis facultas ipsa experiri est melius est
a couple of months just to see if your
in tantum ut si duobus mensibus te
concerns are valid or are you so dead
de valet neque enim tibi et mortuus est
set against this kind of idea I mean I
Et ratio huius dico adverso
love the idea of Wikipedia I love that
ut diligas idea amoris Vicipaedia
social aspect of sharing and fried I do
socialis communicationis et ego frixum
too and I and I use Wikipedia often I
et quoque quod uti non saepius Vicipaedia
would be willing to give WT social a try
WT operam dare vellet socialis
not interested in paying for it yeah
quia non quaero solvente in yeah
like if they want to get people on board
sicut si volo impetro populo in tabula
they need to open up the doors for say
quod necesse est dicere et fores aperire
three or six months get people sucked in
aut tribus mensibus sex ut homines quadam hauserint
where it's free they start building a
unde illud est liberum quod aedificationem incipere
presence there because so many people I
quia tam multi sunt coram te
think are gonna turn an eye to this and
et putant amet verto Oculus
go I'm not putting up many money for
Non dicam plura dare pecuniam
something where there's only a hundred
Ubi illic 'aliqua tantum centum
sixty thousand people I have to just say
EGO iustus dicere habent sexaginta milia homines
that actually nothing is free no it's
quod prorsus nulla res est libera, non est
true I understand that right way or
Intelligo verum et rectam
another you're paying for it so I would
alio solvente tibi quia sic esset,
rather actually pay money out of my
magis ex re vera solunt pecuniam meam
pocket than to try and be afraid of
temptare sinus quam metuere
where they're making money on my behalf
qua ipsi erant 'faciens pecuniam pro me
like where where are they getting the
ut in quo sunt questus est
money from me existing like like there's
ut sit ibi sicut pecunia ab
on that but there's no way that you're
in illo autem, quod illic 'nullo modo es
gonna be able to say that the data and
agnus dei esse possunt, et quod notitia
how you use their site still isn't going
illorum uteris non tamen quantum ad locum
to be used for somebody's personal game
quis est nam ludus personae utendum est
they said they're not going to sell it
illi dixerunt 'non iens ut vendere illud
it doesn't mean the fact that they can't
non sit eo quod non
have subsidiary companies that utilize
quod uti societates sunt subsidiary
that same information or really Jeff
quod eadem notitia aut vere Jeff
we're getting into speculative this is
erant 'questus est in speculativis,
all speculation and I don't like to go
Non omni speculatione procedere
there and I actually love the idea that
amant enim et ideam, quae
somebody anybody's got to do something
quis suus 'got hoc facere aliquid aliorum
different is coming up and saying hey
et ait heu alia venturus est
you're not stuck with the one choice
Non es adhæsit ad arbitrium unum
there is now going to be other choices
jam futurum aliis electionibus
and maybe this isn't the only one that's
et maybe hoc est quod unus solus est scriptor
gonna exist this is the first of maybe
agnus dei est quod est prima maybe
many I agree knows it there's always
multas illic 'semper assentior scit hoc
going to be changing options I just
Sciemus, sequemurque ut mutantur non solum optiones
there's something about it just kind of
Ibi suus 'iustus aliquid de illo genere
feel thanks to Ray W Nash and our
Ray sentire gratias W Nash nostri
community of viewers for submitting
conventu et pro exhibenda viewers
stories to us this week thanks for
tibi gratias ago pro fabulis nobis hoc septimana
watching the category-five TV newsroom
Genus quinque-vigilantes TV newsroom
don't forget to Like and subscribe for
et velut nolite oblivisci per subscribe
all your tech news with a slight linux
fama tua doce levi Linux
bias and if you appreciate what we do
et si bene agat, quid faciemus
become a patron at e3 on.com slash
e3 on.com facti patronus a VULNUS
newsroom
newsroom
from the category 5 TV newsroom then
tum TV V genus ab newsroom
stash your estimate I'm Ravi Ferguson
LATESCO iudicas me Ravi Tacitus
and I'm Jeff Lester
Jeff ego sum Lester